// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [{
        numb: 1,
        question: "There are ________ tuples in finite state machine.",
        answer: "5",
        options: [
            "4",
            "5",
            "6",
            "unlimited"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Language of finite automata is.",
        answer: "Type 3",
        options: [
            "Type 0",
            "Type 1",
            "Type 2",
            "Type 3"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Moore Machine is an application of:",
        answer: "Finite automata with output",
        options: [
            "Finite automata without input",
            "Finite automata with output",
            "Non- Finite automata with output",
            "None of the mentioned"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "In mealy machine, the O/P depends upon?",
        answer: "State and Input",
        options: [
            "State",
            "Previous State",
            "State and Input",
            "Only Input"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "Mealy and Moore machine can be categorized as:",
        answer: "Transducers",
        options: [
            "Inducers",
            "Transducers",
            "Turing Machines",
            "Linearly Bounder Automata"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "Which one among the following is true ?<br>A mealy machine",
        answer: "has less circuit delays",
        options: [
            "produces a language",
            "produces a grammar",
            "can be converted to NFA",
            "has less circuit delays"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 7,
        question: "The ratio of number of input to the number of output in a mealy machine can be given as:",
        answer: "1",
        options: [
            "1",
            "n: n+1",
            "n+1: n",
            "None of the mentioned"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 8,
        question: "Which one among the following is true ?",
        answer: "Moore machine has no accepting states",
        options: [
            "Mealy machine has accepting states",
            "We can convert Mealy to Moore but not vice versa",
            "Moore machine has no accepting states",
            "All of the mentioned"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 9,
        question: "The total number of states and transitions required to form a moore machine that will produce residue mod 3.",
        answer: "3 and 6",
        options: [
            "3 and 6",
            "3 and 5",
            "2 and 4",
            "2 and 5"
        ]
    }, {
        numb: 10,
        question: "The output alphabet can be represented as:",
        answer: "∆",
        options: [
            "δ",
            "∆",
            "∑",
            "None of the mentioned"
        ]
    },
];